1 guinea fowl
bye
goodbye all good
has 1 Meeting with members now
and let's go
and then my brother
wind that
the man is too fancy
Bauducco's money to do that there
standard
ah lie
the money is from Bauducco
the money is from Bauducco food
who works with cs
a microbiology
well applied within BFFs is what makes the difference
so that we can
one hundred and fifty days as a boss
which is way above the caraca brownie market
ours is good for guys
it's tastier than the first one
in my opinion
everyone who received the brownie already from the site
already received with this filling
I look at this product here brother
not my product
but i think at first it's creating demand brother
now a point we get right
and a lot here
we need to release Charlie Brown
Brown and Zé
in the sense of being a treadmill product
then we will create a wish in this here
Brother
absurd brother
it doesn't become a flavor that's on the mat
I think it will work better you called kid
makes a lot of sense man
I will already
march on site
I create cota
people think we go
the proposal is this
it's not this
speaks baby ó
listen here man
in the next steps I will read
thinking of making a website for Charlie Brown
it can
this trap tells you to do this
o then closed bro
I'm going to hit here with Caio
so worth bro
we are with brother
satisfaction
congratulations is us
well i'll march people
you need the knees
people